In him,
I saw that
my books truly hold some kind of power.
It's my genes,
his mission.
My name is Bie Fan.
I'm a fan of Mr. Fang.
His books kept me company growing up.
He's the one who got me through
the toughest days of my life.
But...
but...
his depression is completely fake.
I just heard him say he's fine.
These fans are totally brainless.
Just like that Bie Fan.
They aren't very bright either.
The second he cries,
everyone believes he really has depression.
Then he can sell his books.
Mr. Fang.
I know you must be feeling
very, very upset right now.
You're a man of letters, right?
But they made you take off your pants,
eat sausages,
and shave your beard.
You've been through a lot.
But what I want to say is,
all the crap we take today,
we will one day
make them pay back in spades.
Just like you, since I was a kid,
I've always loved literature.
I know how hard it's been
for you to get this far.
So...
It's been tough, bro.
Here's the thing, Mr. Fang,
let me show you something else.
This
is Bie Fan's previous live stream data.
300,000 concurrent viewers.
Trending at the top!
"Fang Haowen fan saves a life by jumping off a bridge"
That's got tens of millions of views.
Just listen to that.
Most importantly, Mr. Fang,
your book, What Is Success?
sold over 20,000 copies in just an hour.
How many copies that book sells...
what does it have to do with me?
Jin Furong is exploiting me, don't you get it?
I want this book to sell well,
don't you guys get it?
I get it, we all get it. So,
isn't this grand live stream event
called Farewell Rehearsal: Upgraded Edition?
We're going to use this live stream
to promote your new book,
and slap them in the face with it!
Tell me, tell me.
With this level of hype,
what's the minimum we could sell?
Tell me! Give it to me!
300,000.
Mr. Fang, are you happy with this number?
Come on, give us a smile.
Smile.
I... I thought it was just...
I just wanted to be a little dramatic.
Who... who smashed this computer?
300,000! 300,000!
How many copies your book sells...
what does that have to do with me?
Next time you show someone data,
could you use your own computer?
Psycho.
Ms. He,
why did Mr. Fang commit suicide?
To tell you the truth,
Mr. Fang has a very serious illness
called depression.
So you have to...
You have to help him more.
If you encourage him more,
it'll ease his pain a bit.
Depression?
He's totally doomed then.
That's hard to cure.
Remember back in our village,
there was a cow named Fangfang?
Didn't she die of an illness?
Her calf got depressed.
The meat was super tough.
Didn't you eat some too?
What's up? Whose cow is depressed?
What are the symptoms of depression?
Symptoms?
Crying. Crying over nothing.
Their mood is just terrible.
Let me tell you,
being short-tempered is an illness too.
The worst is when they're always smiling.
It's called smiling depression.
Hard to cure.
You have no idea when he's actually happy
or when he's not.
What's up? Whose cow...
Then what can I do for Mr. Fang?
Nail this live stream.
Memorize the lines I gave you.
As long as you don't drop the ball on stream,
Mr. Fang will get better.
Memorize them well.
I definitely will.
Mr. Bie Fan, Mr. Fang.
We can head to the rehearsal now.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Let's go. Let's go.
Mr. Fang...
I know you're happy,
but stop grinning all the time.
What do you mean?
I read your second book.
Well, that makes me pretty happy. Was it good?
Well...
it didn't seem as good as the first one.
Now I'm upset.
No, please don't be.
I'll keep reading.
It might get better later.
I guess so.
To you, this second book
is indeed hard to grasp.
These little poems are mostly
my reflections on life.
Is that why you got sick?
You... you...
You'll understand if you read slowly.
My mom says, "Cure it if you're sick.
Prevent it if you're healthy."
Your mom is right.
Isn't this great?
Pretty healthy, right?
Thanks for trusting me.
And coming to the live stream with me.
After my second book is published,
I'll give you a copy.
And write you a nice dedication.
I'll treasure the book you sign for me.
I'll place it right next to my mom's ashes.
Mr. Bie Fan.
Can we go over the script now?
Y-You don't need to call me Mr.
They all call me Master Bie.
Okay, Mr. Master Bie.
Can we head over there now
to go over the script?
Sure.
We should go over the script. Let's go.
Going over the script is fine.
This way, this way. Don't be nervous.
We do need to go over the script.
Mr. Fang!
Over here, here, here!
Let me walk you through the rundown first.
When the live stream kicks off,
the first thing they'll see
are four beautiful dancers.
They will represent The Four Arts,
which symbolize Mr. Fang's talent,
all-encompassing!
My brain
isn't working well.
Mr. Master Bie, come hit your mark.
This balcony up here
was custom-built just for you.
A 1:1 replica of your home!
To correct your slip
and fall from that day!
You'll descend like the God of Literature
slowly from above.
Don't worry, the wire is very safe.
Haowen.
What do you think?
How's the set design?
Wasn't much, just a few hundred thousand.
Any other questions? Just ask!
Everything else is fine.
Right, um, earlier,
you mentioned that...
that thing holding me up, the wi-something?
The wire. The wire.
Is the wire safe?
Are you kidding? Our boss's team
was brought in from Hollywood.
Over there, it's US dollars every day.
You earn it, but don't dare spend it.
It's pretty boring.
What I mean is,
are we sure this re-wi is safe?
Of course!
If something happened, how could we keep working?
Unhook him.
If it's really safe,
do you think later on,
you could pull me up a bit higher?
Like, the higher the better.
The higher you pull me, the more dangerous it looks.
And the more dangerous it looks,
the more the audience might pity me.
The more they pity me,
the stronger their desire to buy the book!
Do you know what I mean?
You're planning to sell it as your posthumous work, huh?
Let me tell you,
back when we were in Hollywood,
for Jet Li and Jackie Chan,
we were the ones who decided how high to pull them.
Safety first.
It's not a joke.
You think we just pull you as high as you want?
Okay, okay, okay.
Pangpang, Pangpang, Pangpang.
Hello, Pangpang.
Do we have any drinks here?
For our brothers from Yawei.
Hand some out.
Okay, I'll pass them out in a bit.
Alright.
Thanks a lot.
No problem.
We're setting this spot right here.
It's not moving.
Nobody touch it.
Mr. Fang, I wouldn't tell anyone else this.
You can show off these chicken feet,
but whatever you do, don't eat them.
They were prepped for the bridge jump.
We don't have a fridge. They've gone bad.
Okay, okay. Thanks, bro.
Thanks, thanks.
No worries, we're all family here.
A Zu.
Boss Lei's relative.
Let me know if you need anything.
Will do, will do.
Where's the producer?
What's up?
I said, where are the box lunches?
We have no energy to dance without food.
Big brother, you gotta stand up for us.
We're starving!
Wait, how could there not be any?
I remember I didn't just get you box lunches.
I even added a big chicken leg for each of you.
Wait, who is it?
So greedy.
Such a glutton.
Don't you know it's one box lunch per person?
So greedy.
Who are you talking about?
What the hell are you yelling about?
What about it?
What do you even do here?
What's wrong with me eating?
Eating is fine,
but you can't eat four big box lunches!
I'm a martial artist.
Nothing wrong with me eating more, right?
I'm Bro Fangtan. You don't know me?
What's so special about Bro Fangtan?
Bro Fangtan or not,
you still can't just eat other people's
four big box lunches!
What crew preps exact portions with zero extras?
Have you ever even worked on a set?
You're as fat as a pillar.
Go away! Stay back.
Producer! Producer!
I am the producer!
Alice!
Coming, coming.
What's up, bro?
Is this your guy?
A Zu, come here.
Yeah.
He's yours?
Right.
Is he really this unprofessional?
I've worked on film sets for years,
I've never seen anyone so unprofessional!
What's going on?
When I was on "Northeastern Police Story",
the chef there gave me six buns.
Really? What the hell are you doing?
On such a big set,
why do you have him managing the box lunches?
What?
What do you even do?
What's your job? Huh?
A Zu, hurry up and apologize to
Bro Fangtan. Right now!
What are you looking at me for? Apologize!
I'm sorry.
Do you have a drumstick in your mouth?
Spit it out! Apologize!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, bro.
What's going on? All this yelling.
We're trying to work here.
Can't you see?
It's nothing, it's nothing.
Come give me a report.
Alice, hurry up.
Who's this line producer?
He looks unfamiliar.
He's my cousin.
He's one of us.
I told you about him before.
Is he professional?
Don't just hire relatives blindly, alright?
What do you mean?
So my relatives aren't your relatives?
No, no, no.
I didn't mean that.
Then go ahead and fire him.
I'll just quit too, alright?
You can't quit.
I'm telling you, don't look for me again!
Alice.
What is wrong with her! Unbelievable.
Lissy!
Hello, Boss Hu!
Why are you calling me from a different number?
No, let me tell you,
my artist is doing a live stream sale today,
and the money will be here right away.
I'll pay you back by tomorrow at the latest.
Hello? What leg?
What? What?
The signal is bad in the studio!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
Wait...
Who are you?
Me? I'm the singer you guys hired.
Who?
The singer.
Le-oh-le... Boss Lei!
Boss Lei!
What's up?
What... what's going on?
No, who is this guy?
Isn't he the singer?
No, didn't I ask for
Liang Long from Second Hand Rose?
Second Hand Rose?
Liang Long?
With that booking fee?
Can you even afford him?
That's enough, bro.
You two haven't paid a single cent!
Boss Lei.
I advanced all the money for this live stream!
True.
Okay, how about this?
If this stream goes viral,
Liang Long, Jackie Chan, raptors, dragons!
I'll bring all of Jurassic Park to you!
Alright?
We... we're definitely gonna go viral! Viral!
Besides,
that Bro Fangtan,
didn't I get him for you?
Girls,
have a bite to eat first.
I bought you some McDonald's.
I... I didn't know earlier
that the food was yours.
If I had known,
I'd have laid on the ground so it wouldn't spill.
It's fine, Bro Fangtan.
These chicken feet taste pretty good too.
Really?
Let me tell you, these chicken feet
are mustard-flavored.
They're sour and spicy.
So delicious!
Really?
Bro Fang,
do you know martial arts too?
Oh, Little Qi.
You really know what to ask.
It's not just about knowing martial arts.
Right now, if three or five thugs
tried to get close to me,
they couldn't even get close.
Look, let me show you.
Look at this brick. See it?
Watch closely. One, two, three!
Holy crap!
How was that?
Not a scratch.
See that?
His head is really hard.
Look at him showing off.
That brick is obviously fake.
It's a prop brick.
Fake?
Mr. Fang,
did you change your clothes?
Yes, I did.
Are you wearing underwear?
Isn't that question a bit presumptuous?
If I'm not wearing underwear, am I going commando?
No, no.
I mean, are you wearing our Sandao?
Actually, last time I already
showed you guys once.
But I still want to emphasize
that I'm a man of letters.
Last time,
you only showed what the underwear looks like,
but you didn't demonstrate its functions.
Alright then, let me ask you,
how am I supposed to demonstrate
your underwear's quick-drying function?
Like last time,
splash water on my underwear by the river?
Just splash it right on stage?
You're very presumptuous.
For today's live stream,
Sandao spent the most money.
Quick-drying, refreshing, breathable.
With a subtle fragrance.
You can't leave out a single word.
You have to make him smell the underpants.
Otherwise, forget about the placement fee.
Boss Zheng!
What is it?
I mean, you already took the money,
but you're not doing your job.
I know, I know.
The Four Arts, standby.
One minute and forty seconds.
Countdown.
Push the stream.
Five thousand. Ten thousand.
Master Bie.
Stop copying things over there.
Go stand in the wings for now.
What are you doing?
The Four Arts, get ready. Hit your marks.
Lighting, change the lights.
Mr. Fang.
Please stand behind the large book.
Okay, okay.
My stomach hurts a little.
My stomach hurts.
My stomach hurts too.
What do we do?
Countdown, 64 seconds!
Sound, cue the music!
I don't... No...
Hold on!
My stomach...
Online viewers just broke 100,000!
Stage, cue the dry ice!
Wait! Wait!
Dry ice is ready.
I need to go to the bathroom!
You can't go! You can't go!
The stream's about to start!
Hold it in!
You can't go! You can't go!
You can't go!
No, no, I need to use the bathroom!
You can't.
You can't. Hold them back!
You can't. Hold it in!
You can't.
Don't go, don't go.
I've been mopping all day. What did you all eat?
Look at all this puke on the floor.
We just had some hot and sour chicken feet.
Those weren't hot and sour.
The chicken feet were just sour!
I'm telling you,
we definitely can't stop the livestream now.
Think of something. Anything!
Don't film them. Film the stage!
There's nothing on the stage.
What are we supposed to film?
Then what do we do?
Ten seconds left!
That won't work. Have the cleaning lady fill in!
Me fill in? How do I do that?
Three, two, one.
Welcome to Fang Haowen's livestream debut!
Massive giveaway event!
Jump!
Both of us.
Smile.
Change.
The numbers are going up!
Dance! Dance!
Move it!
Alice, Alice, you're up.
Hello, my darlings!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Accompanied by The Four Arts...
A Zu's...
graceful dance moves...
we finally welcome
Fang Haowen's livestream debut!
As you can tell from our first act...
Alright.
Please click follow in the top left corner!
Follow us so you won't get lost!
Next up,
please welcome our main star, Mr. Fang Haowen!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Fang Haowen.
Thank you for all your encouragement yesterday.
I'm someone who knows how to be grateful.
So today, I've prepared
some special gifts for you all.
But livestreaming to sell things
isn't our true intention.
We just want... Alice?
Speak, speak.
Mr. Fang,
before you have a heart-to-heart with them,
we've invited an old friend of yours.
Who?
Mr. Fang!
Who took a dump here?
Oh, Mr. Fang!
I ran my mouth a while ago
and hurt you.
I almost drove you to depression.
I'm so sorry!
No need, no need, no need!
It's fine, it's fine.
Today, I want to use water instead of wine
to toast you!
No need!
A whole bottle in one gulp.
Mr. Fang, a 500ml bottle of water,
downed in one gulp!
That's too bad for your health!
Mr. Fang, you don't believe me?
You don't think I can chug it all?
Right?
You guys don't believe me either, huh?
None of you believe I can chug it? Fine!
Here I go!
Okay, okay, okay!
Today, for my big mouth,
I apologize to you!
That's enough, that's enough!
That's enough! Bro, that's enough!
No!
I don't think it's enough!
Mr. Fang, let me show you my sincerity!
Bring me the brick!
You...
What... what are you doing? This...
First, I shouldn't have shot my mouth off
and cursed you!
Take that for showing off!
Director!
Keep going, keep going, keep going!
Guys,
that's not sincere enough.
Come on! Come on!
A-again! Hit me again!
Smash it! S-
Smash it!
Keep going! Smash it!
Underworld regime control!
My youngest uncle...
Who?
My dear partner...
The Huanglong River faction all have Bluetooth!
Are you...
B-bro...
He's bleeding!
Bro Fangtan!
A-Alice...
Alice, you're up!
What a great start!
Come on, everyone, let's give...
Bro Fangtan a like for his hard work!
Fangtan.
You two go backstage and rest.
Okay, okay.
Enough small talk.
Mr. Fang is backstage preparing now.
He's preparing to meet and talk with us...
in a very special way.
Alright, but before that, let me...
give you all a bonus! Lift it up!
Alright, alright.
What are you doing?
I'm really bleeding and no one cares!
It's fake.
What do you mean fake?
It's fake! It's all fake!
That's enough.
Your opening just now... it was pretty good.
But it had a slight flaw.
What were you doing?
Why were you so happy?
A-and "Who?"
Who cares who it is?
Why did you say "Who?"
Who do you get this from?
You can't act like that.
Does that look like depression?
You were way too happy!
When you go on stage later,
you must make sure...
to speak out your inner pain.
You have to express it!
H-how do I express it?
Cry! You cry!
Don't you know how to cry?
I'm not an act—
Stop pinching me!
That's just muscle memory.
It doesn't reach the tear ducts.
Don't you get it? You're a grown man!
If you don't cry, who'll pity you?
Who... who has the time to read what you write?
Or look at you!
Can you promote our Sandao now?
Did you forget you're the finale?
Let me tell you,
depression,
Fang Haowen,
is your biggest selling point.
What are you thinking about?
Will they believe it?
Let me tell you, netizens these days have no brains.
Just like that Bie Fan.
Low IQ.
Just cry.
Once you cry and act all pitiful,
everyone will believe you have depression.
Only then will your books sell.
You sell the books,
I'll... I... we...
You know what I mean?
That's enough! Hurry up.
Stop spacing out. You're...
You're just one step away from success!
Cry! Look miserable! Show some pain!
I'll punch you!
Okay, hold on.
Alright, now let's...
turn our attention to Mr. Fang.
Depression. Sadness.
Agony.
Mr. Fang is step by step,
step by step facing his fears,
climbing up to where he once fell.
That night,
I was lonely.
Lost and helpless.
That night,
I stood on the roof,
ready to end my life.
But as I was falling,
I couldn't bear to let go.
I regretted it so much.
I thought,
I poured my heart out for over a decade.
The insights on life I've written down
haven't been seen by the world yet.
I teach others how to succeed,
yet I'm not successful myself.
So I figured my first book
still had many flaws.
I poured my heart out again and wrote my...
wrote my second book,
"I Have ""No"" Talent".
Coincidentally,
just when I thought
I was tired of this world,
right when I was about to end it all,
I met my fan,
Bie Fan.
In him,
I can see that
my book truly holds a certain power.
It's my genes,
his mission.
My name is Bie Fan.
I'm a fan of Mr. Fang.
His books kept me company growing up.
He helped me get through
the hardest days of my life.
But,
I'm telling you, netizens these days have no brains.
Just like that Bie Fan.
Not very smart.
The moment you cry,
the moment you play the victim,
everyone will believe you have depression.
Then we can sell the books.
But,
the fact that he has depression is fake.
He's lying.
He just said he's fine.
He said these fans
don't have good brains either.
They have the same IQ as that Bie Fan.
Whatever, it's not very high.
What was I saying? As long as he cries,
everyone will believe
he really has depression.
Then he can sell the books.
He says...
What... what are you talking about?
Uh, my friends,
don't listen to little Bie Fan's nonsense.
He's a fool.
He's a silly Bie Fan.
Uh, he... he...
is indeed very nervous on stage.
He's a bit confused.
Just... just spouting nonsense.
Alice,
whether the depression is real or not,
should be left to the doctors to decide.
But the perks in our stream
are absolutely real!
Babies,
when watching our stream,
whatever you do, don't forget to grab the perks!
Boss Lei, all the books are being refunded!
What? All the books are refunded?
Yeah. It's fine if they're refunded.
Come on, post the links!
Post whatever we have!
Post the trash bags!
No, I... I... I...
I... I don't understand why. I...
I... I don't have depression,
so you won't... won't buy my books?
This... this... this...
This makes... makes absolutely no sense!
He definitely has depression.
Who jumps off a building if they're fine?
You guys can seriously,
carefully,
take a good look at my book.
I really... I really am talented.
Our Jile razor
shaves away your future!
I...
In elementary school, I...
In elementary school, I already won
first prize in the city's essay contest.
They were just saying over there...
I...
For over a decade, I've kept writing.
I really... I...
really try to understand Mr. Fang.
No, it's not like that.
I... I very diligently
treat every single word I write.
I just want everyone
to read my book, that's all.
I...
Traffic has reached 500,000!
Post it! Post whatever we have!
Post it!
Come on!
Whether it's depression or mental illness,
I... I never said I had depression!
They said it!
Without depression,
would he be wearing just his boxers
and jumping off the eighth floor?
Don't tell me... No!
Does me having depression or not
really matter that... that much?
Just close your eyes and buy it!
Very severe depression!
Can everyone just let me finish?
Give me a chance to explain!
He Jiahuan, get the hell out here!
Sir, you can't go in there. We're in the middle of...
Get out of my way!
He Jiahuan, get the hell out here!
Let's see you stream!
What are you doing?!
We're streaming! You can't stop the stream!
Stream!
This has gotta be fake.
It's obviously staged.
I've seen this trick a million times.
Just another streaming stunt.
He Jiahuan!
Boss, it's time.
Should I go on?
What should I sing?
Sing whatever the hell you want!
What're you looking at?!
Say one more word and I'll kill...
Imitate Jackie Chan? Imitate Panglong?
Imitate a dinosaur!
Imitate whatever you want!
Okay, okay!
You little bastard, I'll kill you when I catch you!
Shut up!
Wh-What?
Catch him!
Who is it?
Where did this brute come from?
Bro Fangtan, aren't you gonna stop him?
Didn't you say three to five guys...
...would be no problem for you?
I-I did say three to five guys are no problem.
B-But aren't they all holding clubs?!
Wait,
we've got over 500,000 viewers online!
Hello, friends in the livestream!
This is Ah Long, bringing you
something you've never heard before...
Velociraptor's "The Moon Goes Too Far"!
Take a good look at my book!
My book!
Me? What's wrong?
What the hell? What's going on?
You brutes!
I didn't say I wouldn't pay it back!
You're gonna beat him to death!
Are you blind? Kill him!
Are you ready?
Spicy! Spicy! Spicy!
He was yelling "pull" just now, right?
Hold it down as we go!
Come on, one, two, three!
Spicy!
What happened?
This... this is way too chaotic!
Stream! Keep streaming!
Still talking? Beat him up! Beat him to death!
I'm Zheng Zhiren, head of Sandao Underwear!
Our Sandao underwear is...
Quick-drying, refreshing, and breathable!
Lightly scented!
He doesn't deserve such good underwear!
I'll beat you to death!
Not paying back what you owe!
He doesn't deserve them!
Doesn't deserve them!
Our Sandao underwear is...
Quick-drying, refreshing, and breathable!
Lightly scented!
The exact same style as Mr. Fang!
Buy ten, get ten free!
Lightly scented!
Everyone, buy Sandao underwear!
The link is up now, hurry and buy!
Where are you going?
Someone messed with my brother.
The food... the food's burning.
Spring and death,
the most frequent imagery in poetry.
They foster and complete each other,
yet dissolve and destroy one another,
writing off hope completely.
They run in a blind panic.
I am now
committing suicide by poetry.
Everyone, you must read my second book.
It's really good.
Values are crumbling.
Society is completely out of balance.
I heard
he slept with a woman
just to get this opportunity.
I admit he pursued me passionately.
How could I write a blurb for him?
He really has no talent.
He actually plagiarized and published my work.
I'll smack you!